{
    "id": "c2fe625725014c96ae69d73f12c9558e",
    "title": "Classification Of Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The jury has announced its verdict. Jury is a .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun",
                "collective noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "45c5635e3ba4480584fcb6cd5d6c391c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sharon makes models from clay. Sharon is a ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "collective noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "074e93526f394a899538b21cd38f1700"
        },
        {
            "question": "Donald took out his pen and began to make notes. Pen is a .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "material noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20f2e4715ef247cc9832917ac38ec866"
        },
        {
            "question": "The crocodiles in the river snapped angrily at the boat. River is a .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proper noun",
                "abstract noun",
                "common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fcedaba8687549339020884c67e3f741"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys on bicycles delivered pamphlets. Pamphlets is a ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "collective noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2114a19e907a4b3f972973c08f3f7d14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cleopatra was known for her beauty. Beauty is a / an .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun",
                "common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8511bc5125814449beceb0a89df730d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Always speak the truth. Truth is a ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "39c82a34dba54ebeba944a0a6701a8cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Nile overflows its banks every year. Nile is a ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proper noun",
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c25ef11f9989468fbfaac5d2bbea429a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I believe in his innocence. Innocence is a ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bb6ca724f0bb477bb638fd1229d4ad4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant has great strength. Elephant is a .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun",
                "common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "63f975fd438b46968c8b61f7e5cbb23d"
        }
    ]
}